[{"question": " so, which of this kitchen stuff is mine?", "answer": " this bottle opener.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " and?", "answer": " and it&#146;s a magnet!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " look at that!", "answer": " how weird is that? y&#146;know? you&#146;re moving in with me and have the one thing i don&#146;t have. it&#146;s like uh, in a way you-you complete me  kitchen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": "  you complete me kitchen, matey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " ross, i know what you&#146;re thinking.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " that she&#146;s gonna move in with you and maybe then she&#146;ll fall in love with you and then when she finds out you&#146;re already married, she&#146;ll just be happy. y&#146;know? you&#146;re just, you&#146;re very sad.", "answer": " oh&#133;my&#133;god! i-i see what this is! you are in love with rachel!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " what?!!", "answer": " of course! it all adds up! i mean you you&#146;re obsessed with her. it&#146;s always, &quot;ross, what are you gonna do about rachel?&quot; &quot;ross, why-why are you moving in with rachel?&quot; &quot;when are you gonna confess your secret marriage to rachel?&quot; you want her!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": " hey rach, aren&#146;t these candlesticks  mine?", "answer": " no-no, i bought those.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": " ohh! yeah, i forgot.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": "  no-no-no, that&#146;s great! i&#146;ll be there monday. and thank you again!  okay.   umm, that was the head of the paleontology department at n uh, y, uh u!", "answer": " wow! uh what, did he uh, say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " well remember that paper i had published last year on sediment flow rate, huh? they loved it.", "answer": " well, who wouldn&#146;t?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i know! anyway, they asked me to be a guest lecturer! i mean it&#146;s temporary, but uh, if they like me it could lead to a full time job. how great would that look great on a mailbox, huh? &quot;professor geller.&quot;", "answer": " yeah, professor and mrs.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " and mrs.?!", "answer": " oh! yeah, y&#146;know you and ross are still married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " what?!!", "answer": " just kidding!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " oh, what&#146;s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, you know that psychic i see?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " well, she told me that i&#146;m gonna die this week, so i&#146;m kinda bummed about that.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " yeah, and i know you guys don&#146;t know a lot about psychic readings, but that one is pretty much the worse one you can get.", "answer": " phoebe that&#146;s crazy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " i can&#146;t believe she would say that too you.", "answer": " yeah honey you don&#146;t believe her do you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " i don&#146;t&#151;she said y&#146;know that i&#146;d have triplets! but she also said one of them would be black.", "answer": " just out of curiosity did she tell you how you&#146;re gonna go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": "  hey everyone!", "answer": " oh hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh that&#146;d be great. sure!", "answer": "  &quot;there are three primary theories concerning sediment flow rate. each of these theories can be further subcategorized into two distinct&#133;&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " oh, this is it. this what&#146;s gonna kill me.", "answer": "  &quot;&#133;subcategories. the first of these subcategories is&#133;&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": "  uh ross! are there uh, are there naked chicks on that piece of paper?", "answer": " no! why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " well, i&#146;ve just never seen a guy stare so hard at a piece of paper that didn&#146;t have naked chicks on it.", "answer": " ohh! okay! okay.  &quot;there are three  primary theories concerning sediment flow rate.   each of these theories  can be further subcategorized  into&#133;&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " why don&#146;t you open with a joke?", "answer": " open with a joke? it&#146;s a university, not a comedy club!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " wait a minute, hold the phone! you&#146;re not talking about chuckles university?!", "answer": "  okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " ohh! we&#146;re kidding! oh, we&#146;re kidding!", "answer": " ross, hey you know what might make it less boring?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " thank you!", "answer": " some uh, some visual aides.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " oh-ooh-ooh! y&#146;know what&#146;s a good visual aide?", "answer": " please don&#146;t say naked chicks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " why not?!", "answer": " i-i-i don&#146;t even know why i bother to talk to you guys about it. y&#146;know what? i&#146;m just gonna do it on my own with no naked chicks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! any good mail?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " yes, you got something from the screen actor&#146;s guild.", "answer": " ooh, it&#146;s probably a residual check, hey can you open it for me, i&#146;m kinda&#133;.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": "  &quot;benefits lapsed.&quot;", "answer": " hmm that&#146;s weird. i don&#146;t remember being in a move called benefits lapsed.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " okay, it&#146;s not a check. they&#146;re saying your health insurance expired because, you didn&#146;t work enough last year.", "answer": " let me see that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": "  oh, i can&#146;t believe this! this sucks! when i had insurance i could get hit by a bus or catch on fire, y&#146;know? and it wouldn&#146;t matter. now i gotta be careful?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " i&#146;m sorry man, there&#146;s never a good time to  stop catching on fire.", "answer": " all right well, i guess i gotta go get a job. i&#146;m gonna go see my agent.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay, make sure you look both ways before you cross the street.", "answer": "  &#133;look both ways before you cross the street.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey pheebs, you&#146;re still alive! how are you doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " pheebs, what-what are you doing?", "answer": " i was preparing you for my&#151;didn&#146;t you think i was dead? did that not come off?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " oh yeah, scared the hell out of me. i thought we&#146;d lost you forever. pheebs, you lie down?", "answer": " yeah, thanks. and listen, can you do me a favor? could you just umm, wake me up in a couple hours, y&#146;know if you can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " monica!", "answer": " hmm?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " did-did you take these back?", "answer": " no-no, i-i just, i liked them so much that i went out and bought some for myself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh yeah, they&#146;re really great! aren&#146;t they?", "answer": " i loved them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": "  hello!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " how&#146;d the lecture go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " it went great! and i didn&#146;t need any jokes or naked chicks either!", "answer": " wow, that&#146;s great ross, i&#146;m sorry we weren&#146;t more supportive before.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " i knew all i had to do was let the material speak for itself. everyone&#146;s all, &quot;ross you have to be funny and sexy.&quot; well, i proved them wrong! and now, i&#146;m gonna pass the news onto joey and chandler.", "answer": " that you&#146;re not funny or sexy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": "  hey estelle, listen&#133;", "answer": " well! well! well! joey tribbiani! so you came back huh? they think they can do better but they all come crawling back to estelle!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " what are you talkin&#146; about? i never left you! you&#146;ve always been my agent!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " oh well, no harm, no foul.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " estelle, you gotta get me some work. i-i lost my health insurance.", "answer": " all right, first thing we gotta do, damage control.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " well, i think uhh, someone out there may have been bad mouthing you all over town.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  hey! so estelle lined up a bunch of auditions for me tomorrow and i&#146;ll have my health insurance back in no time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " that&#146;s great, but shouldn&#146;t you be on the toilet right now?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " what&#146;s wrong with you?", "answer": " nothing! well, i-i got this blinding pain in my stomach when i was lifting weights before, then i uh passed out and uh, haven&#146;t been able to stand up since. but um, i don&#146;t think it&#146;s anything serious.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " this sounds like a hernia. you have to&#151;you-you go to the doctor!", "answer": " no way! &#145;kay look, if i have to go to the doctor for anything it&#146;s gonna be for this thing sticking out of my stomach!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " that&#146;s a hernia.", "answer": " why did i have to start working out again?  damn you 15s!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " well, we&#146;re a little early, the lecture doesn&#146;t end for 15 minutes.", "answer": " yeah, but y&#146;know we could sneak in and watch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " what the hell are you doing?!", "answer": " look, i was nervous! you guys had me all worried i was going to be boring! i got up there and they were all like staring at me. i opened my mouth and this british accent just came out.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah, and not a very good one.", "answer": " will you-will you please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " dr. geller, kurt rathman, i&#146;m a professor in the paleontology department here.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " do you have a moment to talk about your lecture?", "answer": "  i&#146;m sorry, i&#146;ve got plans with my sister.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": "  right, will you excuse us for one moment?   what are you doing?", "answer": "  oh, you can have an accent and i can&#146;t?!  top &#145;o the morning to ya laddies!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey, will you grab me a cruller?  sit down! will you go to the hospital?!", "answer": " dude! hernia operations cost like, a lot probably. besides it&#146;s getting darker and more painful, that means it&#146;s healing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " i will loan you the money. just go to the hospital and let&#146;s just get that thing&#133;pushed back in.", "answer": " thank you, but it would take me forever to pay you that money back and i don&#146;t want that hanging over my head. okay? besides, as soon as my insurance kicks in i can get all the free operations i want! yeah, i&#146;m thinking i&#146;ll probably start with that laser eye surgery too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " what&#146;s going on?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " oh joey&#146;s got a really bad hernia, but that&#146;s nothing a little laser eye surgery won&#146;t fix!", "answer": " look, i&#146;m telling you if i put my hand on my stomach right here  it doesn&#146;t hurt that bad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " hey! maybe you&#146;ll die!", "answer": " sure, now i&#146;m scared.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " no, we can go together! just don&#146;t wait too long though, okay? &#145;cause i&#146;m outta here sometime before friday.", "answer": " yeah, but i don&#146;t wanna die!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " gimme &#145;em!", "answer": " no! they are mine!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " you stole them from me!", "answer": " you stole them from me!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " you just wanna each take one?", "answer": " yeah that seems fair. we never use them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": "  look, i really need some help, okay? why? why did i have to speak in a british accent?! what do i do?", "answer": " well&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " why don&#146;t you phase it out? yeah, fade the accent out and people will think you&#146;re, y&#146;know, that you&#146;re adjusting to life in america.", "answer": " yeah, i mean, come on ross, no one will even notice. i mean they&#146;re probably not even listening!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " they&#146;re not listening too me?", "answer": " of course they&#146;re listening to you! everybody listens to you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " monica you really think i should try this phasing out thing?", "answer": " i think you look fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " whenever you&#146;re ready.", "answer": "  okay. &quot;hey, timmy, i&#146;ve got a surprise for you.&quot; casting director #1: hold it. i&#146;m sorry, the surprise is a new swing set, if you could play it a little less&#133;intense?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " so that&#146;s why i feed my dog purina one! pick up a bag today!  casting director #2: that&#146;s where you pick up the bag.", "answer": " exactly. casting director #2: no, the line is pick a bag, so you need to pick up the bag.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " or, i could just point to it! huh? blah, blah, blah, purina one, point to a bag today.  i didn&#146;t get it, did i? casting director #2: no.", "answer": " yeah, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " hi. i&#146;m joey tribbiani; i&#146;m here to audition for  man. casting director #3: you mean dying man?", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " okay, come on, do it one more time!", "answer": " really? really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " okay!   &quot;hello ross, this is dr. mcneeley from the fake accent university, we&#146;d like you to come on board with us full time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " listen to this! my reading was wrong, i&#146;m not going die!", "answer": " really?! how do you know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " because my psychic is dead! she must&#146;ve read the cards wrong!", "answer": " oh, i&#146;m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " listen, i&#146;m really glad you got the part.", "answer": "  thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " but are you sure you can do this?", "answer": " yeah! and hey, thanks for coming with me. and thanks again for helping me take a shower.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " now, is that never talking about it again?!", "answer": "  hiya!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey joey, we&#146;re ready for ya!  joey, this is alex he&#146;s going to be playing your son.", "answer": " hi alex!  and uh, as you can see my hands are not in my pants.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " okay.  all right uh, alex now when joey says his line, &quot;take good care of your momma son,&quot; that&#146;s your cue to cry. got it?  all right, let&#146;s do this.  a crew member:  scene 5, take 1.", "answer": " and action!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " &quot;take could care of your momma son.&quot;  &quot;take could care of your momma son.&quot;  &quot;come on son! your momma&#146;s good people!&quot;", "answer": " cut! alex, remember you&#146;re supposed to cry. can you cry for us this time?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " all right, from the top. a crew member: scene 5, take 2.  a crew member: take 36 is up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " all right! let&#146;s try this again! you ready joe?", "answer": " ah, just one thing umm, is it all right with you if i, if i scream right up until you say action?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " uh sure.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " action!", "answer": "  &quot;take good care of your momma son.&quot;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": "  hello?", "answer": "  hello, is ross there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " uh no, he&#146;s not. can i take a message?", "answer": " yes, this russell, ross&#146;s divorce lawyer, just tell him that since i haven&#146;t heard from him, i assume he&#146;s decided to give the marriage a try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " what&#146;s happening to your accent?", "answer": "  come again? what&#146;s-what&#146;s this nonsense?   all right, i&#146;m-i&#146;m not english. i&#146;m from long island. i was really nervous and the accent just uh, just came out. i&#146;m sorry. so, if we could just get back to the lecture. umm, were there any questions?  about paleontology.  all right, look i was just trying to make a good first impression. obviously, i screwed up. but what you guys think of me is really important because i&#146;m-i&#146;m hoping to get a permanent job here. so if you just give me another chance to make a good impression&#133;", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " ross!! are you crazy?! i am still your wife!! what, were you just never gonna tell me?!! what the hell is wrong with you?!!!! ugh, i could just kill you!!!!", "answer": "  well, hello rachel! ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " have you really done this before?", "answer": " yeah! yeah! yeah! you just take a big, big swing. now, don&#146;t hold back. (he dons his protective helmet", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey-hey-hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " we&#146;re just celebrating that joey got his health insurance back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s6/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}]